(Amy:)Oh. Okay.
(Bernadette:)Wipe that smug smile
off your face.
(Howard:)Maybe I'm happy
that so many people turned up
(Howard:)to help the less fortunate.
(chuckles)
(Emily:)Are you and I close
enough for me to say...
(Bernadette:)That he's an ass?
He beat you to it.
(Soup Kitchen Manager:)I was wrong.
A large group had to cancel.
(Bernadette:)Oh, great.
We'd love to help.
(Bernadette:)Wipe that smug smile
off your face.
(laughing):
I can't!
Look at us!
(Penny:)Our first Thanksgiving
as husband and wife.
(Leonard:)I know.
(Leonard:)I feel so grown up.
Sweetie, you are grown up.
Really?
(Leonard:)How many grown-ups do you know
who have Mr. Spock oven mitts?
(Leonard:)Hey, the recipes
are on my iPad.
(Leonard:)Will you pull 'em up?
Yep.
(Penny:)What's the code?
My birthday.
(Penny:)It's not working.
(Leonard:)It's just the four digits...
month and day.